goshen.edu 2016-06-24

# Web Privacy Policy | Goshen College | Goshen College

**Effective Date of Current Policy:**  August 6, 2015  
**Date this Privacy Policy was last revised:**  August 6, 2015

This Privacy Policy describes the personally identifiable information that Goshen College (“GC,” “we,” “us”) collects through our Website and Systems accessed through [goshen.edu](https://www.goshen.edu/) (all other systems see paragraph 1) and how we use that information. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to our online information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with the GC Website and Systems, and does not apply to any of our practices conducted.

## **The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

GC collects two types of information about users of the GC Website and Systems:

(1) Personally identifiable information: Certain services, such as the Request Information Form, to which you may gain access through the GC Website and Systems, may require you to provide personally identifiable information. We use such personally identifiable information to respond to your inquiries and to send you information about our courses and programs. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive emails from us, please refer to the paragraph below headed “Changing or Deleting Personal Information.”

If you contact us by email through the GC Website and Systems or submit any information, such as a phone number, through the GC Website and Systems, we will collect any personally identifiable information that you transmit to us and we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and we reserve the right to use your email address and phone number, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to communicate with you. In addition, we may send by email important administrative information regarding the GC Website and Systems or services to users who have provided us with their email addresses. Such information may be important to your use of the GC Website and Systems and is regarding our ongoing relationship with you.

(2) Non-personally identifiable information: We use this information to conduct typical marketing activities, including behavioral and personalized retargeting. We may retarget visitors to our website with additional advertising after they visit our site or if they use search engines to look up terms related to our programs. We may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information in connection with the GC Website and Systems. Our web pages may incorporate “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” or similar tracking technologies (collectively, “pixel tags”) that allow us or our agents to track the actions of users of our GC Website and Systems. We may also aggregate your information with similar data collected from other users to help us improve our GC Website and Systems, and the services that we provide through our GC Website and Systems.

## **Cookies**

A cookie is a simple text file placed on your computer by a web server. We use cookies for a number of reasons, such as:

  * to learn more about the way you interact with the GC Website and Systems content;
  * to help us improve your experience when visiting the GC Website and Systems;
  * to remember your preferences;
  * to identify errors and resolve them; and
  * to analyze how well the GC Website and Systems is performing.

The key reason for using cookies is to make visits to the GC Website and Systems more convenient, more efficient and user-friendly for you.

## **How do I reject and delete cookies?**

The privacy settings in your browser will enable you to customize your cookie settings, including deletion and disabling them. Typically, you will find the controls under the browser’s ‘Options’ or ‘Preferences’ menu. The exact level of customization will depend on your browser. Refer to your browser’s help facility or to the website operated within your country of residence.

Changing your cookie settings, including deletion and disabling them, may mean that the functionality of the GC Website and Systems and your ability to use some of its features is affected. You will still be able visit our website, but you may not be able to access all of the content and some of the functions may not operate correctly.

## **Use of Information**

We may use the information collected for the following purposes, in addition to those described above:

  * Tailoring the GC Website and Systems to user needs and improving our service;
  * Generating data and reports about usage of the GC Website and Systems and its content;
  * Supporting the functioning and security of the GC website and our network systems; protecting our rights, property, or safety or those of others; and research; and
  * Providing customer service and application assistance to prospective students.

## **How We Disclose the Information We Gather**

We reserve the right to provide the information we collect to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain services (e.g., web hosting and maintenance services, improving the GC Website and Systems and its features, or customer service) on our behalf. We also reserve the right to disclose such information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of the GC Website and Systems or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of GC and its affiliates, its and their partners and employees, the users of the GC Website and Systems, and the public.

We may share the information we gather with third parties, including our Affiliates or Partners, to perform functions and provide services to us including, without limitation, outreach and assistance to you with regard to selecting a program of interest, completing an application, and other related activities. We may provide collected information, including personally identifiable information, to those third-party Affiliates and Partners for those purposes. In addition, we may share with third parties information about the use of the GC Website and Systems and its content that is aggregated or anonymized so that it does not identify any individual user.

## **Changing or Deleting Personal Information**

If you would like to change your personal information or if you no longer wish to receive materials from us or want your personal information removed from the GC Website and Systems, please contact us at [info@goshen.edu](mailto:info@goshen.edu). Alternatively, when you receive materials from us by email or other communications you can make use of the “opt out” or “unsubscribe” provision in such communications so that we know that you no longer wish to receive such materials from us.

## **Security**

GC will use reasonable security measures to assist in protecting against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personally identifiable information which is under our control. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we undertake commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and GC’s servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the GC Website and Systems. You provide all such information entirely at your own risk.

## **Revisions to Privacy Policy**

GC reserves the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit by referring to the “Date this Privacy Policy was Last Updated” date at the top of this page. Your use of our GC Website and Systems constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms. Your continued use of this GC Website and Systems and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

## **Links to Other Websites**

The GC website contains links to other websites that are independently owned and operated, and are not part of the “goshen.edu” domain. GC is not responsible for the privacy practices, activities or content of such independent websites. Any links to external websites and/or non-GC information are provided solely as a courtesy and should not be construed as an endorsement by GC of the content or views of the linked materials. The materials on these independent websites are the opinion of the specified author(s) and are not statements of advice, opinion, support or information of GC.

## Website content and copyright information

The Goshen College Web pages are maintained by many departments and organizations across campus and are regularly updated and improved. As it is available, new content is added. Although we attempt to keep information in the Goshen College Web accurate, you assume the risk that the information and materials on this Web site could be incomplete, inaccurate, out of date, or may not meet your needs and requirements.

The personal employee, student and student group home pages maintained on the Goshen College Web servers are the sole responsibility of the users who make information publicly available on the Web. The personal home pages and the opinions or information contained therein, as well as any pages linked from the Goshen College Web, are the creation of the person or persons maintaining the pages and do not necessarily represent the opinions of Goshen College.

With respect to any information available from this Goshen College Web site, neither Goshen College nor its employees assumes any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process disclosed, or represents that its use would not infringe privately owned rights.

Most graphics, images and text, and all Goshen College-related seals, logos and wordmarks are protected by trademark or copyright. They may not be reproduced in any electronic or written medium without the prior consent of Goshen College.

* * *

_Adapted with permission from Georgetown University School of Continuing Studies_

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our practices regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [info@goshen.edu](mailto:info@goshen.edu).
